so I was in Hollywood since I was eight years old and somehow there became this like narrative
Amanda Seals is difficult and this went on for like a very long time so much so that even last
year like there was a whole campaign to like send this message that I'm difficult and there became
this narrative of well where there's smoke there's fire like there must be a truth to this if it's so
consistent and the truth is is that I was surrounded by people who are bought so it's like yeah
yeah I was difficult like and I realize now that I'm excised from it just how wildly regular it is
to just have very little integrity very little insight to have really honestly just very little
concept of anything other than the expansion of your brand or your name or your money like that
is the goal what award can I get what deal can I get like honestly like there is just so little
analysis done beyond the acquiring of any of those things so so it's like whatever rumors were said
about me being difficult like they're right because I was always an outcast I was always not like that
and and and I'm sure that that is that was difficult the celebrities that y'all
wrap your hearts around for so many of them it's it's just the art or it's just the talent
but for very very very few of them is it actually the heart life comes at you fast